

Aditya Shekhawat

To work with an organization would give me an opportunity for personal growth an...

- 🛎 adityashekhawat824@gmail.com 🤳 8955573508
- 9 Navjeevan colony khatipura, 302012 Jaipur Rajasthan

Education

Commerce | I.P Stream Apr 2013 - Mar 2014

St.Anselms north city school, Jaipur

B.sc in hotel Management Jun 2015 - Apr 2017

Pacific university, Udaipur

Internship From Malaysia Nov 2016 - Mar 2017

Eastin groups of hotels, Malaysia Kaula Lampur

Employment

Front office assistant 2017 - Apr 2018

Samode group of hotels, Jaipur

Front office assistant Jul 2018 - Aug 2019

Trident Oberio Jaipur, Jaipur

Awarded with team of quater by Arjun Oberio

Front desk manager Oct 2019 - Mar 2020

Royal Heritage Haveli, Jaipur

Property Manager Oct 2021 - Sep 2022

Dhun Jaipur Rajasthan, Jaipur

Restaurant manager / Property Nov 2022 - Feb 2023

operational Manger

Cafe Bae/ Las Vegas hotel, Jaipur

Profile

Up-to-date training in health and hygiene best practices. Friendly hospitality worker committed to customer satisfaction. Enthusiastic, energetic professional with exceptional communication skills. Highly experienced and knowledgeable with hospitality technology and software.

Personal details

Date of birth

August 30, 1997

Place of birth

Jaipur

Gender

Male

Nationality

Indian

Skills

- Flexibility and Adaptability
- Tolerance: Stress Tolerance.
- Self Motivated Honesty and Integrity
- Communicating
 Communications Skills.

Punctuality. • Team Work Skills.

Languages

English, Hindi,

Hobbies

State Level Swimmer

Courses

Spanish and French Languages

Jan 2023

Learning New Language for Knowledge and growth

Food and Beverage services

Aug 2015

Almost done 20 ODC with all groups of hotel at Udaipur

Internships

Food & beverage Trainee

Sep 2016 - Mar 2017

The Leela Udaipur, Udaipur

Attend basic program as Trainee

Jul 2014 - Feb 2016

The Oberio Uday Villa's, Udaipur

Attended Basic Training wine certificate program

Bar Tender Trainee

Sep 2016 - Mar 2017

Taj Lake place, Udaipur

Extracurricular activities

Football player

Oct 2022

S.M.S Stadium Jaipur, Jaipur

Planning football helps growth in team management

Traveller

Rajasthan, Rajasthan

Aug 2017 - Apr 2023

Traveling different city to collect information and knowledge thats help me to entertain my Guests.

Achievements

While working with hotel Industry I awarded so many times. Also have very good relationships with all hotels and restaurants in city, which help me to attend my guests very well

References

References available upon request.

- State Level Athletic
- Traveling Different countries to enjoy their Food and Traditional Culture

Qualities

- Self Motivated Honesty and Integrity
- Very Trustworthy Man
- Fast Learner
- Always well Groomed
- Very good relationship with people of different Service Industry